

Contact Me:

8285820428

asifjmi14@gmail.com

Izzat Nagar Bareilly, UP,

INDIA

Social Profile

Linkedin.com/in/mohd-asif-b50088174

Technical Skills

MS OFFICE and ICT

Skills

Communication, Analytical, Interviewing Skills, recruiting (IT & non-IT), Critical Thinking, Salary Negotiation & Convincing Skills, Emotional intelligence, Decision-Making, Collaborations, Problem Solving, Compassion.

Languages:

English, Hindi, Urdu, Arabic

MOHD ASIF

HUMAN RESOURCE



Objective

Energetic entry-level Human Resource Specialist. Assist with administration of HR operations for prestigious organization. Accepting a challenging role in a professional organization where i can utilize and enhance my skills and competencies in conjunctions with the company's goals and objectives.



Experience

2018-2019

Human Resource Experience – HR Trainee

Assisted with administration and operations of HR department for fast- paced business. Helped in Recruitment process and on boarding of new Employees, Induction, Orientation Program and Facilitated Campus drive recruitment in Manufacturing Industries (Eaton power Quality, Solara Active Pharma Sciences, Strides Pharma Sciences, Vadilal Group industries).

01-2020-03-2020

Management Trainee-HR - IT Jumbo Consultants, Delhi

Managed Human Resource Functions and worked on Recruitment life cycle, Interviewing, coordinating, Back ground verification, onboarding of new employees, joining formalities, Documentation, employee life cycle.

Worked on IT recruitment from entry level to higher level.

Total 6 month experience in Human Resource including HR Trainings or Internships (end-to-end Recruitment, IT Recruitment, Joining formalities, on-boarding, Induction, Orientation, Talent Acquisition, Employee Relations, Employee Grievances, Employee Wellness, Employee Engagement and Exit Formalities.

Awards:

Best Campus Award in NIC, Jamia Millia Islamia University

Hobbies:

Playing Cricket, Volley Ball, Acting, Travelling, Book and Articles reading

Date: 25/07/2021

Signature:



Education:

2017-2019

MSW- HUMAN RESOURCE (Cgpa 8.54)

Pondicherry University

Excelled in Human Resources Management

2013-2016

B.A. (Cgpa 8.25)
Jamia Millia Islamia University



Project

Employee Retention and Work Life Balance: Strides Pharma Sciences, Pondicherry

Employee Retention and Work life Balance project is concerned with Industrial Employment. Retention Strategies and policies play a crucial role to retain the best talent that are the most valuable assets for the company's growth.

25-07-21 16-08-21 **TATA Consultancy Services- TCS**

TCS iON Career Edge – Young Professional Certificate Course

Bharathidasan University- 25/06/21

Attended two-day Virtual Workshop on Industrial Relations Practices in Indian Scenario.

Rotary Bangalore Sneha-5/06/21

Attended webinar on Statutory Compliance applicable to Shops and Commercial Establishments.

Bharathidasan University- 13/05/21

Participated in Two Days Workshops on HR Practices in Digital Era.